<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GuideSlayTheSpire</string>
    <string name="strength_build_explain">    In the Strength build the main things you need to do is gather cards which will increase the strength of the Ironclad, in meantime increasing your strength will increase the damage output of each attack cards you have. The cards you needed such as : </string>
    <string name="strength_build_explain2">While using the Flex cards, you can negate the debuff effect which lose your 2 strength after using it. To negate that you can easily use the Panacea card, it can be negated by some relics to such as Clockwork Souvenir or Orange Pellets Relic. </string>
    <string name="strength_build_explain3">You can use any Attack cards to deal a big damage since you already buff your strength, Try using some good cards, such as Reaper, since it can give you amount of heals base on the unblockable damage you dealt to the enemies. </string>
    <string name="defend_build_explain">    In the Defend build the main things you need to do is build the deck around the Barricade cards or get the Calipers Relic, since it will stack up your block number without losing it when turns end. If you get the card/relic you will just need to collect the increase block cards, such as Entrench since it will double your block numbers.</string>
    <string name="defend_build_explain2">   Since you already build your deck with the cards needed on the top, you can easily kill the enemies by using Body Slam card. Body Slam will deal damage based on the block numbers you have. And a additional Juggernaut cards is good to for the damage</string>
    <string name="rupture_build_explain">   In the Rupture build the main things you need to is build the deck around the Rupture cards. Rupture will give +1 strength for each time you lose HP while using a card, and you need cards which will deal damage to yourself while damaging the enemies. Offering and Bloodletting are good supports card for this build since it can give you mana while decrease your HP.</string>
    <string name="rupture_build_explain2">  You can add Brutality card too, since it will give you an additional to draw a card while you lose 1 HP, it will a good synergy with the rupture build. And you need Reaper card to give to an additional HP based on the unblockable damage, Hemokinesis is a good attack card for this build too. But be careful of your HP.</string>
    <string name="searing_build_explain">   In the Searing Blow build the main things you need to is build the deck based on the upgrading the Searing Blow. Searing Blow can be upgraded by many times, so it will give a lot of damage after each upgrade. You need to keep you cards in deck low, since you will need to draw Searing Blow for dealing a lot of damage.</string>
    <string name="searing_build_explain2">  There are some good cards, that will be good synergy with the Searing Blow build such as Armaments and Apotheosis, since it will give you an upgraded to the card, so you can increase its damages.</string>
    <string name="searing_build_explain3">  You can try to add Double Tap or Dual Wield card, it has a little of mana require and it can will be a good synergy too for the Searing Blow, extra copy of the upgraded Searing Blow won\'t be hurt right.</string>
    <string name="zero_mana_build_explain"> In the Zero Mana build the main things you need is cards which can deal damage while using 0 mana. There are some cards that are good for this build such as Anger, Clash. Anger can give you a duplicate of the card while dealing damage to the enemy.</string>
    <string name="zero_mana_build_explain2"> You can add support cards like Rage or Berserk, Rage can give you 3 block each time you use the attack card. You can use the Double Tap cards too, since it will give the same effect while using an attack card.</string>
    <string name="zero_mana_build_explain3"> If you have a lot of mana, you can combine this build with Strength Build, since it can deal a lot of damage while using 0 mana, it can increase the damage too.</string>




</resources>
